Good morning!
Hana wakes up super early.
She wakes up at 5 in the morning.
When she wakes up, she's sleepy,
but there's a place where she can open her eyes.
That's the kitchen.
And Hana makes miso soup.
The miso soup starts from where you get the soup stock.
From last night, take the kelp soaked in the water in the pot and the cut bonito flakes to make dashi.
Puku puku puku, puku puku puku.
Put the pot with the kelp on fire.
When bubbles come out, take the kelp out of the pot.
This time, make the fire stronger.
Wait a minute, then turn off the fire.
Then, take out the bonito flakes from the bottom of the pot.
This remaining hot water is the soup stock.
Papa, taste it.
It's good.
Well then, itadakimasu.