Today, the highest temperature in Seoul rose to 36 degrees, and it was the hottest day of the year.
This heat will continue until tomorrow, and it is expected to cool down a little on the next day.
Last night, an Asian flight from Jeju to Busan refused to land right after the start of the late night landing ban.
Some passengers came all the way to Incheon Airport, then took a bus and went back to Busan.
On the second line of Incheon subway, where the accident was going on from the first day of operation, another accident occurred where power supply was cut off.
Some sections were stopped operating.
A 4-year-old child who suddenly collapsed after wiping his teeth was found to have been violently assaulted by his mother for a long time.
The police applied for an arrest warrant for the mother.
In the Saenuri Party General Assembly, a single candidate for the Bipartisan Party was decided.
In the preliminary election of the Democratic Party of Korea, a change occurred in which the main member, Song Myung-kyul, was eliminated.